const questions: Array<{
  question: string;
  answer: string;
}> = [
  {
    question: "“Adventure of Sherlock Holmes” was written by which writer?",
    answer: "Arthur Conan Doyle",
  },
  {
    question: "Which mountain range is the longest in the world?",
    answer: "Andes",
  },
  {
    question: "What vehicle is Volkswagen best known for in the world?",
    answer: "Beetle",
  },
  { question: "Which musical legend is Jay-Z married to?", answer: "Beyonce" },
  {
    question: "According to the commercial, “what is the fabric of our lives”?",
    answer: "Cotton",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What animal is known for its ability to change color to match its surroundings?",
    answer: "Chameleon",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which popular soft drink was originally created as a medicine in the 19th century?",
    answer: "Coca-Cola",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What fruit is known as the “king of fruits” and is banned in many hotels and public transportation in Southeast Asia due to its strong smell?",
    answer: "Durian",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What prime time soap opera aired on CBS about the saga of the Ewing family and its massive oil empire based in a major city of Texas?",
    answer: "Dallas",
  },
  {
    question: "Which natural disaster is measured with a Richter scale?",
    answer: "Earthquakes",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The smallest bone in the human body can be found in which body part?",
    answer: "Ear",
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the richest person in the world as of 2021?",
    answer: "Elon Musk",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who was the famous nurse known for her work during the Crimean War and is considered the founder of modern nursing?",
    answer: "Florence Nightingale",
  },
  { question: "What is the largest bone in the human body?", answer: "Femur" },
  { question: "Larry Page is the CEO of which company?", answer: "Google" },
  { question: "What is the largest island in the world?", answer: "Greenland" },
  {
    question:
      "Which fashion brand made the “Genius Jeans” that became part of the Guinness World Records?",
    answer: "Gucci",
  },
  {
    question: "Which animal can be seen on the Porsche logo?",
    answer: "Horse",
  },
  { question: "What animal’s milk is pink?", answer: "Hippopotamus" },
  {
    question:
      "Before becoming President, Barack Obama served as a U.S. Senator from which state?",
    answer: "Illinois",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the title of the classic Greek epic attributed to Homer, telling the story of the Trojan War?",
    answer: "Iliad",
  },
  {
    question:
      "A narrow strip of land with sea on either side, forming a link between two larger areas of land is known as an",
    answer: "Isthmus",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who won the Academy Award for Best Actor for his role in the 2020 film “Joker”?",
    answer: "Joaquin Phoenix",
  },
  {
    question: "Which country is known as the Land of the Rising Sun?",
    answer: "Japan",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What vegetable used to be known as “Peasants Cabbage”, reflecting its status as a common food for the poor in many parts of Europe?",
    answer: "Kale",
  },
  { question: "What was Superman’s birth name?", answer: "Kal-El" },
  {
    question: "Who did Forbes name the youngest self-made billionaire in 2019?",
    answer: "Kylie Jenner",
  },
  {
    question: "What fashion fad did the 1983 film “Flashdance” make popular?",
    answer: "Legwarmers",
  },
  { question: "Who painted the Mona Lisa?", answer: "Leonardo da Vinci" },
  {
    question: "Who was the first woman to win a Nobel Prize (in 1903)?",
    answer: "Marie Curie",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of these games includes the phrase “Do not pass go, do not collect $200”?",
    answer: "Monopoly",
  },
  { question: "Who was the first man to moon walk?", answer: "Neil Armstrong" },
  {
    question:
      "What is the world’s largest supplier of athletic shoes and apparel and is named after the Greek goddess of victory?",
    answer: "Nike",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the home of the Greek Gods?",
    answer: "Olympus",
  },
  { question: "Thor was the son of which God?", answer: "Odin" },
  { question: "What is the state vegetable of Texas?", answer: "Onion" },
  {
    question:
      "What classic video game requires you to eat all the dots throughout a maze?",
    answer: "Pac-Man",
  },
  {
    question: "Which name is rapper Sean Combs better known by?",
    answer: "P. Diddy",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What word shares its meaning for putting out a fire and satisfying one’s thirst?",
    answer: "Quench",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What writing tool preceded the invention of the metal-nibbed pen and is made from a moulted flight feather?",
    answer: "Quill",
  },
  {
    question:
      "This social news and discussion website is known for their community building characterized by “r/”",
    answer: "Reddit",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the northernmost capital city in the world?",
    answer: "Reykjavik, Iceland",
  },
  {
    question: "Which watch company has a pointed crown as its logo?",
    answer: "Rolex",
  },
  { question: "What do you call a group of fish?", answer: "School" },
  {
    question: "Which cartoon character lives in a pineapple under the sea?",
    answer: "Spongebob Squarepants",
  },
  {
    question: "What type of alcohol is traditionally used in a margarita?",
    answer: "Tequila",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the smallest size bed available in the United States?",
    answer: "Twin",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What type of flowers are often associated with Holland and most commonly symbolize deep love?",
    answer: "Tulips",
  },
  { question: "What is the official animal of Scotland?", answer: "Unicorn" },
  {
    question:
      "This is a psychological phenomenon that describes the feeling of unease when confronted with something that is almost human but not quite",
    answer: "Uncanny valley",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the smallest country in the world?",
    answer: "Vatican City",
  },
  { question: "What name does deer meat go by?", answer: "Venison" },
  { question: "What are the bones in your spine called?", answer: "Vertebrae" },
  { question: "What is the capital of New Zealand?", answer: "Wellington" },
  {
    question:
      "On Sunday 18th June 1815, which famous battle took place and also shares a name with a brand of sparkling water?",
    answer: "Waterloo",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What popular children’s puzzle book consisted of detailed pages of crowds where one must look for a red and white striped man?",
    answer: "Where’s Waldo",
  },
  {
    question:
      "This is an example of an imaging procedure that uses radiation to produce pictures of the inside of the body",
    answer: "X-Ray",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What Marvel Comics features a superhero team of mutants with superhuman abilities generally manifesting during puberty?",
    answer: "X-men",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What food item is made when combining heated milk with bacteria in incubation at warm temperatures?",
    answer: "Yogurt",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What was the name of the country in Central and Southeast Europe that translates to “Land of the South Slavs”?",
    answer: "Yugoslavia",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What creature do most players first encounter in the popular kids game Minecraft?",
    answer: "Zombies",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What 2016 Disney Animated buddy cop comedy film features Nick Wilde and Judy Hopps?",
    answer: "Zootopia",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What country features the 355-foot Victoria Falls and is also known for their hyperinflation crisis?",
    answer: "Zimbabwe",
  },
];

export default questions;
